in the west good afternoon
на западе добрый день
that you have a detachment, let's first
что у вас отряд давайте сначала 3
greet 3 and I will be good afternoon
поприветствуйте и буду добрый день
that what good afternoon I say good good
что что добрый день говорю добрый добрый
asgora good afternoon my name is andrey I am
азгора добрый день меня зовут андрей я
from the city of khmelnitsky ukraine
из города хмельницкий украина вы с
which city of russia
какого города россии
from luhansk graph
из луганска графе
somewhere
где-то
in the world there are Bagan
в мире есть баганского
northerners  in siberia there is a city of lugansk in
северяне в сибири есть город луганск в
russia and in ukraine or a year
россии и в украине или год
ass about count 6
попкой о графе 6
lugansk is not far from the rostov
луганск это недалеко от ростовской
region is not in from lugansk which in
области нет в с луганска которые в
ukraine is either now occupied or
украине так то ли сейчас оккупирован или
siberian luhansk to hell like that
сибирского луганска до ада типа того
which you understood in ukrainian promises you
которые вы в украинское понял сулит вы
really from
реально из луганска до пацаны
You can somehow confirm from Lugansk to the boys, I
можете как-то подтвердить я
really understood in order not to breed, to
действительно понимал чтобы не разводить
drown, having drunk the post, I’m interested
утопать попив же посту мне интересно вот
in talking with the boys from Luhansk, having twisted
с пацанами из луганска пообщаться
such a problem in any city,
покрутив в любом городе такой
but I didn’t take my passport with me,
проблемой а паспорт с собой не брал
well, come on, who is who you are now the
хорошо давай давай то кто кто вас сейчас
head of this Lugansk republic
глава этой республике луганской а
ok okay yes let's conclude I really
окей хорошо да давайте вывод я очень
like to meet people from the Luhansk and
люблю встречать людей из луганской и
Donetsk republics tell me
донецкой республики расскажите мне
and  the history of your republic how it was
историю своей республики как она
formed what date who
образовалась какого числа кто ее
formed it a
образовал
good question let's which way
хороший вопрос давайте которые образом
the mouth of the occupation of Russia began not well,
началось уст оккупации россии не ну вот
what date did your republic begin here
какого числа началась вот ваша
who created it when the
республика появилась кто ее создал когда
fourteenth year did it
четырнадцатый год ли это поклоны
remember bows and who created it
запоминал а кто ее создал
who created
кто и создал
it is necessary around the worlds  and remember to think with us
надо по мирам и запомни подумать у нас
they simply shouldn’t have been remembered
их просто не должно было надо вспомнить
because I remember that she was the SBU the last
потому что я помню что она сбу прошлый
head of the republic is Igor Plotnitsky
глава республики это игорь плотницкий
and before that there was some kind of head there,
а до этого еще был какой-то там голову
not just no one can tell the history of the LPR
не просто никто историю лнр не может
how it appeared, by the
рассказать как она появилась
way, a good question of a car  this
кстати хороший вопрос автомобиля в этом
year, for example, Ukraine appeared
году мы вот например украина появилась
on August 24, 1991, the Supreme Council of the
24 августа 1991 года верховный совет
Ukrainian Soviet Socialist
украинской советской социалистической
Republic, that is, the parliament of the RSR,
республики то есть парламент рср
elected by all people, it proclaimed the
избранные всеми людьми он провозгласил
independence of Ukraine and the creation of an
независимость украины и создание
independent Ukrainian state, and
независимого украинского государства а
who and when proclaimed the LPR density is
кто и когда провозгласил лнр густота
interesting to me
интересно мне
to say that this is what the LPR was
нашему сказать это то что лнр была
recognized by Russia in the 19th year but  if in order
признана россии 19 го года но если чтобы
to admit it is necessary that it was created by who
и признать надо чтобы оно создалось кто
and when it was created
и когда ее создал
who will remember
кто вспомнит
who k
кто к
[music]
[музыка]
2020 the month of May all for
2020 год май месяц все за игорь
Igor Venediktovich
венедиктович
some Igor Venediktovich created for you in the
какой-то игорь венедиктович вам создал в
month of May the LC
мае месяце лнр
this is the People's Republic they and the mountain of the
это же народная республика они и горе
Venedikts the Czech Republic
венедиктов чешская республика
is  before the good questions, of course
это перед хорошие вопросы у меня конечно
,
поставили
I was asked, I know you there was some kind of referendum,
я знаю вас там был какой-то референдум
so it
так
turns out Igor Plat is not there then the
получается игорь плат нет тогда
carpenter was still
плотницкого еще булатов был
damask steel [music]
работу было недобрый вы волыну но когда
tell me the
то есть это вы образовав скажите мне
date it was formed there
дату туда образовалась она
then it was called done yard then
тогда называлась сделано ярда то
yes on 12 it is 12
да по 12 это 12
11 you already had a referendum so one and
11 вас уже был референдум так один и
became May
стал мая
as far as I remember the trend was here before
насколько помню трендом было сюда раньше
they created it
у них
there in April look you
там в апреле создалась смотрите у вас в
created the Luhansk People's
апреле создалась луганская народная
Republic in April someone  created it and
республика кто-то ее создал и
seized power there and held a referendum on the 11th of
захватил власть там и 11 числа провел
who was this someone who
референдум кто был этот кто-то кто
held a referendum
проводил референдум
on held a referendum
по проводил референдум
[music]
[музыка]
the mayor of luhansk is unlikely that you are watching
мэр луганска вряд ли вы смотрите
russia the right to make a film so I went to the
россии право делали фильм вот я зашел в
wikipedia article this is of course not a reliable
статью википедии это конечно не надежно
source there squeaks the lnr was
источнику там пищит лнр была
proclaimed on April 27, 2014 they don’t
провозглашена 27 апреля 2014 года не
write by whom when how what people
пишут кем когда как какие люди
proclaimed the lnr
провозгласили лнр
but at the same time where there is no public 12k breaking
но при этом где нет публики 12к ломая
[music]
[музыка]
information one of these people held a
информации один из эти люди проводили
referendum who were these people who
референдум кто были эти люди которые
seized power and proclaimed that they
захватили власть и провозгласили что у
had the LPR now they
них лнр теперь они луганского
held some kind of referendum in Luhansk with weapons in
проводили какой-то референдум с оружием
their hands well I suppose that these people are
руках ну я полагаю что эти люди это
Russians and you are not afraid to say that
россияне а вам не страшно такое говорить
now
сейчас
no well because  here you are in luhansk if you
нет ну потому что вот вы в луганске если
don’t hear russia choose something about the
россия не услышишь выберите про россиян
russians he starts they would
что то он начинает они бы
in theory the moment there is
по идее момент нет
nothing so sure
чего так уверены
at the moment firstly we are an
на данный момент во-первых мы
independent republic they enter the
независимая республика они входят
photo and
фотографию и
secondly I didn’t say features anything
во-вторых я не сказал фичах ничего
illegal
противозаконного
better if I’m a blogger  from the inside I will write down I
лучше если я блогер изнутри я запишу я
can expose you if you expose for
могу выставить вас если выставлять за
blurting or
блюрить или
talking our posting on the Internet
разговорились наш выставлять в интернет
for blurting you or leaving  to smoke
за блюрить вас или оставлять таким
like that just so that there are no problems it
просто чтобы не было каких-то проблем
turns out if you are an independent
получается если вы независимая
republic, yes, how could
республика да это как же вам тогда
Russia not make a referent
россия не делали референт
for you then, since they could crank with bullets, I
так как они могли провернуть пульками я
suppose the locals of the republic itself
полагаю вадька местные самой республики
asked about this if the republics were
об этом попросили если республик
referents on May 11, so the republic you
референты был 11 мая так республика вы
they said it was created then on May 12, that is,
сказали создалась тогда 12 мая то есть
until May 12 there were no authorities of the
до 12 мая не было никаких властей
republic,
республики
what they asked for,
то что там попросил
perhaps the people themselves drew how, but the
возможно сам народ обратил как но сам
people themselves, this is the entire Lugansk region, which
народ это вся луганская область что
means
значит
the people themselves with what form of the mouth of
сам народ с какой форме самому ротом
Russia’s lollipop, so that I’m not the majority, but
леденца россии чтобы я не большинства а
like you  measured this opinion of the
как как вы замерили это мнение
majority of the bun, it’s
большинства булка это
possible that some kind of question held it so
возможно вопрос какой то проводил так
important,
важно
that is, in short, there was nothing that
то есть короче не было ничего что
some people proclaimed to themselves
какие то люди себе провозгласили во
during military armed
время военных вооруженных кита
clashes so they came from Russia
столкновений так пришли из россии
proclaimed the Luhansk People’s
провозгласили луганскую народную
Republic held at gunpoint
республику провели под дулами автоматов
and creams now you have a republic
и кремами теперь у вас есть республика
yes
да
this garbage was below teaches somehow a knockout
это фигня был ниже учит как-то нокаута
well also here I am  and nobody’s business,
ну тоже вот я что и дел не никто я
why I love it when I get on people from
почему люблю когда попадаю на людей из
whom they are burning from the LPR and DPR, I want
которые горят из лнр и днр я хочу чтобы
them to tell me the history of their
они мне рассказали историю своей
republic, how it was created for us,
республики как оно создалось нас оно
it means it somehow appeared, no
есть значит она как-то появилась никто
one can say how it should be from
не может это сказать как должны быть от
specifically what  then here is the open data
конкретно какие то вот открытые данные
from this story, everything is incomprehensible here there are no
из этой истории все непонятно здесь нет
specific surnames there are no specific dates in
конкретных фамилий нет конкретных дат в
this their history, but look there,
этом их историю а вот смотрите там я
for example, I read
например читал в
Russian telegram channels in Ukrainian
украинских telegram каналах российских
telegram channels and what do you have there LPR DPR
телеграм-канал а что у вас там лнр днр
people grab for example and send to
людей хватают например и отправляют на
war like this  military registration and enlistment offices is it true or is it
войну так военкоматы это правда или это
perry and increase it is true why
перри и увеличивать это правда а почему
it’s not there why you stopped they took you away
его нет почему вы остановили забрали
why they don’t take you of military
почему вас не забирают призывного
age we didn’t recognize them for you therefore I
возраста мы их не признавали вам посему
understood everything damn you look older I
понял все блин вы выглядите постарше
understand it
понял
turns out if you are 18 8 years ago you
получается если вам 18 8 лет назад вам
were 9
было по 9
for your throat  then you don’t really remember, and they
для горла то вы толком и не помните и
don’t teach you the history of the LC at school, it
вас в школе не учат историю лнр
turns out, well, while I was at school,
получается ну пока учился в школе мне
everything was only superficially there,
там всё только поверхностно приходилось
I had to eat  they didn’t tell how,
то есть не рассказывали как типа
specifically, who created this LC, they
конкретно кто как создал это лнр
just said that in the fourteenth
просто рассказали что в четырнадцатом
year the republic brings here, or the coat of arms, the
году приносит республика вот или герб
washed contribution here is 3,
умытые вклад вот 3 а
but for example, you are 18 when it
вот например вам 18 когда будет вас
turns out you can pick up a matron,
получается можем могут забрать матрон
so you will go,
еще вы пойдете
I don’t know what choice and according to  there is
я не знаю какой выбор и по имеется
another we have closed borders for people
другой у нас закрыто границ для людей
over if you can’t leave and now from
над если не можете выехать а теперь из
when to
когда
reach a lot of loss vova simple and
достигать много утратой вова простому и
successive earlier but now for now 17 you
череды ранее ну а сейчас пока 17 можете
can go until 17 you can but I just can’t
же ехать пока 17 можно но мне просто не
get a stalemate on to
получается безвыходное положение на в
some extent yes
какой-то мере да а
and you have some friends who
у вас есть какие-то знакомые которые уже
were already older than military age, they were
были старше призывного возраста их
sent, caught and sent to well, and
отправили поймали и отправили на ну и
our friend whose nose was forcibly
нашей знакомой которого именно насильно
taken to the war
забрали на войну
, we have friends who went
нос у нас есть знакомые которые попали
to war there, not exactly on the strong
на войну там не то чтобы прям на сильных
exhaust of
выхлоп
work and climbed
работы и забрались
miners
шахтеров
right from work, after all, and then even the armor
прямо с работы ведь а потом даже брони
worked for us, one person from the
сработало у нас один человек из поселка
village just thought he was not taken away,
его просто подумал а не на забрали
not alive, or there are such  but
не живые или есть такие же погибли
there are those who died in the village of Taleb, but for the sake of
есть погибшие в поселка талеб на а ради
what, here’s how they explain to you for the sake of what this
чего вот как вам объясняют ради чего это
war is going on, a
война идет
war like nura for the sake of protecting us
война типа нура ради защиты над нами
from whom it protects,
от кого защищает
as far as propaganda from beeches explains to us,
насколько нам объясняет пропаганда от
because all the packaging and fuel, that
буки по что вся упаковка и топлива то
is, to receive, but they leave you to die
есть получать но бросают вас умирать
like  close-up, but it turns out
типа крупным планом а вот получается
when you were, well, yes, we don’t remember much 9
когда вы были ну да мы мало помните 9
years when Ukraine was still, well, here you are, as
лет когда была украина еще ну вот вы как
it were, completely part of Ukraine, you were so
бы полностью в составе украины были так
controlled by the wedge, you had some kind of
подконтрольную клине у вас были какие-то
harassment, someone offended you there because of the
притеснения вас там кто-то обижал из-за
Russian language  no, don’t remember, that is,
русского языка нет не помните то есть
everyone freely said there that I
там свободно все говорили что я такого
didn’t have this,
не было
but maybe you have these questions for me
но может у вас есть это вопросы ко мне
as residents of Ukraine,
как жители украины
not docked units and
не купированные части и от конкретно
there are no specific questions from
никаких вопросов нет
us, we are now on the territory of d600
мы сейчас на территории d600
occupied territories, I am in the city of
оккупированные территории я в городе
Khmelnitsky on the free territory of the
хмельницкий на свободной территории
police  and before the
милиции а перед
question, it’s so new, it’s for strong
вопросом таким новый это на сильная
mobilization, which
мобилизация
means the servants we have there tell
да значит слуги у нас там рассказывает
us what we have there, well, Russian propaganda
что у нас там ну российская пропаганда
that we have caught  but we don’t have it,
что у нас вылавливает у нас нет так вот
for example, I pass every day near the
например я прохожу каждый день возле
military registration and enlistment office, for example, this one is right next to the
военкомата например такой прям возле
door, no one is like that, that is,
дверей никто никого не вот так то есть
for example, what to break the agenda so
например что разбить повестке для того
that people clarify their data, that is,
чтобы люди уточнили свои данные то есть
whom to call for, for example, if someone had
кого призывает например если кто-то имел
some specialties  the military, that
какие-то специальности военные так то
is, will recruit from us now people who are
есть наберет у нас сейчас людей которые
enough in the army, so it’s just that I’m a
в армии хватает так вот просто вот меня
person who didn’t serve who doesn’t
человека который не служил который не
understand it, there’s no point in taking and
соображает в этом не нету смысла брать и
throwing somewhere, for example, the one from the cat
кидать куда-то берут например тот у кота
who has so many connections, these are rocket men, so
кто связи столько это ракетчики так
on like this  that is, this is Russian
дальше вот так то есть это российская
shell propaganda, although it was,
пропаганда shell у нас ходят хотя было
for example, that I offended, I don’t know
например такое что я обидел я не знаю
how much it really is, it’s kind of like they went to
сколько она реально что вроде как на
Transcarpathia
закарпатье
there to those who are resting, they handed out a
ходили там тем кто отдыхает раздавали
summons, but I don’t know
повестку но я не знаю
this is also a show I went out in every Ukrainian
это тоже шоу я вышел в каждом украинском
city, it was like this  I’m talking about
городе такое было вот я говорю про
Khmelnytsky, I don’t remember, but we
хмельницкий я не помню только у нас
wanted to go there, the police wanted there
хотели там полиция хотела там
for those who violate the rules of the
тем кто нарушает правила дорожного
road, and there at night there is no where to
движения и там ночью не там где им
hand them  messages like, well, they immediately raised it
вручать повестки типа ну сразу подняли
well, they will take it for a circus like in the army
хорошо это за цырк типа в армии будут
as a punishment, on the contrary, the army
брать как наказание у нас наоборот армии
is considered as an honorary piece of the
считается как почетная штука
law, they get moves, that is, of this type
закона попадают хода то есть такой типа
immediately, rather, everyone fell into doubt,
сразу скорее все пали сомнением это
we won’t have enough people
делать не будем нас хватает людей
who want to go to the army, so then  there are
которые желают идти в армии так то есть
those who have, let's say, a certain
у которых есть и определенные скажем
desire and certain skills, that is,
желание и определенные умения то есть и
such as if you would avoid a city there, you
такого как бы что там город избежишь вы
wanted to hand it to checkpoints there
хотели там на блокпостов там вручать там
for a brush, not to violators of traffic rules,
за brush никому не к нарушителям правил
but immediately
дорожного движения но сразу отказались
refused it, the military said that this is all a circus is
от это военные сказали что это все цирк
not  you need one of
не надо такого из
me what is the name of your channel on the
меня как называется ваш канал на канал
english channel folders
англии папок
once again my last name is andrey andrey andrey
еще раз фамилия меня звать андрей андрей
folders, that is, take it to google and
андрей папок то есть возьмете в google и
type andrey folders and
наберете андрей папок и
so and there you will be
так и там вам покажет андрей попов chat
shown by andrey popov chat roulette andrey popok
roulette андрей попок
experience through Ukrainian, that is, through
опытом через украинскую то есть через
Russian and  ukrainian and andrew
русскую и украинскую и андрей папы
dads get food fell asleep well everyone let's
наберете еда уснули хорошо все давайте
keep enjoying it will be good
держитесь пользоваться будет хорошо
good wrestling waterfall  in and further
хорошо борьба водопадов и далее
like this, read our Ukrainians in the
вот так почитай наши украинцы на
occupied territories,
оккупированных территориях
but they will say something in Russian, the thorns
но они по-русски скажу что-то терновки
heard that
услышали которые
our Ukrainians in the occupied
наши украинцы на оккупированных
territories were the most faithful there for 17 years when
территориях вернейшим там 17 лет когда
this price was part of them for 9
это цена часть им было по 9
ladies who refrain I’ll come Russian before the
дамская кто рефрена приду русские до
wire
проводе
how yours was formed  lnr I don’t know at
как образовалась ваша лнр не знаю в
school they don’t tell the school they will tell
школе не рассказывают школе расскажет
you the coat of arms flag like everything and the neckline I
тебе герб флаг типа все и декольте
’m dying for the lnr
умираю за лнр
ah it was formed it
ах она образовалась
turns out no people narmer evil
получается никакой народ нармер злого
were some armed before Russian
были какие-то вооруженные до российские
you are such militants who you goose or
вы такие боевики которые вас гусь или
captured proclaimed there the lnr and
захватили провозгласили там лнр и
spent at gunpoint  some kind of
провели под дулами автоматов какой-то
pseudo-referendum so that
псевдореферендум так которыми
it has no legal force at all and
юридической силы не имеет ни вообще и
now these same people are thrown to
теперь этих же людей так бросают на
death in order to hide
смерть на то чтобы скрывать
Ukrainian positions in order to
украинские позиции так для того чтобы
save their Russian soldiers and the
экономить своих российских солдатиков а
horse breeder throws these there with cars and
коневод бросают этих там с машинками и
[applause]
[аплодисменты]
[music] of
[музыка]
that  in order to identify the positions of the brute
того чтобы выявлять позиции тем брут
further already
дальше уже
[music]
[музыка]
such print russia russia she is in
такой печатать россия россия она в
h  in the fourteenth year, we began to occupy our territory for this war,
четырнадцатом году начала на эту войну
to kill
оккупировать нашу территорию убивать
our people higher in Donetsk and Lugansk,
наших людей повыше в донецке и луганске
these are all our people, Ukrainian citizens, and
это все наши люди украинских граждан до
there are some there for laboratory assistants who
некоторые есть там к лаборанты которые
cooperated with Russia, before
пошли на сотрудничество с россией до при
during the Second World War, there were also a
во второй мировой войне тоже в россии
huge number of people in Russia who
огромное количество людей которые
collaborated  from Nazi Germany, but
сотрудничали с гитлеровской германии но
if Vlasov’s army was on the Russian
если армия власова было на русской
liberation army, does this mean that
освободительной армии значит ли это что
Russia was all for Hitler, and so often
россия вся была за гитлера и так часто
there are people in the Donetsk Luhansk region
донецкой луганской области есть люди
who, to which laboratory assistants, they
которые до которые лаборанты они
cooperate to perfection, we are such a
сотрудничают совершенстве мы таким
regime, someone from a day and someone from a
режимом кто то из за день и кто то из за
click  then other beliefs, that is, a
клик то и других убеждений то есть
small number of people and they are
небольшое количество людей и они держат
kept in this fear, so all this population
вот в этом страхе так все это население
people cannot freely express their
люди не могут свободно выражать свои
thoughts, do some kind of rallies, so
мысли какие-то митинги делать так таким
they arranged such a life, try to say something there
устроили такую жизнь попробуй там что-то
, and tomorrow no one will
скажи звука и завтра тебя никто и не
who will find justice in these territories there is no
кого правосудия на этих территориях нет
access to some world element of
доступа каким-то мировым же элементом
justice  udiya european court on the right to a
правосудия европейский суд справа в
person to aibo
человека к aibo
o therefore Russians if you want
о поэтому русские если вы хотите чтобы
this all to stop and you must
это все прекратилось а вы должны
stop your country you must
остановить свою страну вы должны своим
tell your rulers not to
правителям говорить не надо не надо
kill people in ukraine they don’t care about
убивать людей в украине им плевать на
this if you are afraid to
этот если вы боитесь
reap me don’t openly help development
жать мне не открыто помогаете развитию
ukrainian channels help which
украинских каналов помогайте какому
channel like us leave
каналу как мы им так тоже оставляйте
comments so like subscribe and
комментарии так лайкаете подписывать и
it will increase the audience and more of
это будет увеличивать аудиторий и больше
your compatriots
ваших соотечественников
will see it it is very important yes to wear
увидит это это очень важно да носить
because first we have to reach
потому что сначала мы должны достучаться
God to the brains of the majority and then
бог мозгам большинства и тогда наступит
real cardinal changes will come
реальные кардинальные изменения
subscribe put like directly  and
подписуйтесь ставьте лайк прямо и муся
the musya of this vorti and ours on the right is sacred
этого ворти и наша справа священна